<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eldiron</title><link>https://eldiron.com/</link><description>Recent content on Eldiron</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Markus Moenig</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eldiron.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Development Blog May</title><link>https://eldiron.com/blog/development_blog_05_29_22/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/blog/development_blog_05_29_22/</guid><description>Eldiron v0.55 I started the month by adding a new 24x24 tile-map to the already existing 16x16 tile-map. The new tile-map has more details, both focus on Ultima 4 / 5 style tiles and are production quality. As always the tile-map is MIT licensed and the full source files can be downloaded here.
Next I started with player handling. Although Eldiron already has a quite powerful node system I mostly focused on NPC behavior (Non-Player-Characters) so far.</description></item><item><title>Development Update</title><link>https://eldiron.com/blog/development_update_04_28_22/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/blog/development_update_04_28_22/</guid><description>Eldiron v0.5 Newly added features:
Completely reworked the Regions view, now has 3 modes for drawing tiles, editing areas and assigning behavior nodes to areas. Regions now support transparency and up to 4 layers of tiles. Working Systems, every character can now call system behavior trees for common functionality (combat, crafting etc).</description></item><item><title>Development Update</title><link>https://eldiron.com/blog/development_update_04_12_22/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/blog/development_update_04_12_22/</guid><description>Eldiron v0.4 Newly added features:
Named behavior trees can be selected via the tab bar at the top of the node graph. New Lookout and Close In nodes. Expression and Script nodes now have a full scripting system behind them. New Systems editor where soon the user can create systems for Combat, Magic, Crafting and so on. Systems will allow the implementation of basic mechanics every character can utilize.</description></item><item><title>About Eldiron</title><link>https://eldiron.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/about/</guid><description>Create your own classic role playing games (RPGs) with Eldiron, a cross platform and open source RPG Creator written in Rust.
Eldiron is currently under development and not yet ready for public consumption. You can follow the development progress on the blog.
Join the community on Discord or support the Eldiron project on Patreon.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://eldiron.com/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://eldiron.com/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/features/</guid><description>Eldiron Creator is a cross platform creator for classic RPG games.
General Features Create single-player or multi-player experiences. Games run on any desktop, device or browser. A sophisticated behavior node system makes it easy to implement any kind of game logic for areas, characters or systems (crafting, magic etc). Nodes are backed by a full-featured scripting language. Eldiron Creator UI Features Tiles Eldiron comes with a variety of tile-maps for your RPG, however you can of course add your own.</description></item></channel></rss>