<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Eldiron RPG Creator</title><link>https://eldiron.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Eldiron RPG Creator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eldiron.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://eldiron.com/blog/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/blog/about/</guid><description>Eldiron is currently under active development and a v1 is planned for the first quarter of 2023. Eldiron is open source and licensed under the MIT.
Features of v1 Support games similar to Ultima 4 / 5 or any game which uses a rectangular grid layout. Eldiron comes with integrated tile-maps or your can use your own square tiles with up to four levels of transparency. Single-player or multi-player experiences. Eldiron has a sophisticated multi-threaded server architecture to allow for as many player or NPC characters as possible.</description></item><item><title>Eldiron v0.7 Pre-Release</title><link>https://eldiron.com/blog/prerelease/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/blog/prerelease/</guid><description>Dear Internet.
I am sorry for the long delay. Eldiron was way much more work as expected, especially due to the internal multi-player design.
I have now released v0.70, an official pre-release with missing features. But it is supported and future versions will be backwards compatible.
You can download it for Windows and macOS here on GitHub Releases.
Linux binaries will be added soon!
Thanks so much for your support and as always you can contact me directly on Discord for support or questions.</description></item><item><title>Development Update</title><link>https://eldiron.com/blog/development_update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eldiron.com/blog/development_update/</guid><description>All is going well and I hope to provide a public pre-release within the next 1-2 months. The core components are done, now it is mostly about fleshing out the node and scripting systems which make up the gameplay (which is quite fun).
What I am working on Many components need some more attention, like the integrated code editor for example, there are of course bugs and the UI need some more work, however it is all coming together nicely at the moment.</description></item></channel></rss>